{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Q1. Which keyword do you use to annouce constants in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. Var",
      "answerB": "B. Let",
      "answerC": "C. Con",
      "answerD": "D. Value",
      "correct_answer": "B. Let"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Q2. How many types of integers are in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. 1",
      "answerB": "B. 2",
      "answerC": "C. 3",
      "answerD": "D. 4",
      "correct_answer": "B. 2"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Q3. Swift integers are presented in all of these bit forms except which of the following?",
      "answerA": "A. 24",
      "answerB": "B. 16",
      "answerC": "C. 32",
      "answerD": "D. 64",
      "correct_answer": "A. 24"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Q4. What type of integer is denoted by Int8?",
      "answerA": "A. Open",
      "answerB": "B. Signed",
      "answerC": "C. Unsigned",
      "answerD": "D. Close",
      "correct_answer": "B. Signed"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Q5. What are numbers with fractional components called in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. Sinking numbers",
      "answerB": "B. Decimals",
      "answerC": "C. Floating numbers",
      "answerD": "D. Fractional numbers",
      "correct_answer": "C. Floating numbers"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Q6. How do you write comments Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. */ and */",
      "answerB": "B. /* and /*",
      "answerC": "C. /* and */",
      "answerD": "D. */ and /*",
      "correct_answer": "C. /* and */"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Q7. What are the collection types in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. Dictionary and array",
      "answerB": "B. Array and library",
      "answerC": "C. Dictionary and library",
      "answerD": "D. Library, dictionary and array",
      "correct_answer": "A. Dictionary and array"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Q8. Which of these is not a control transfer statement in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. Break",
      "answerB": "B. Continue",
      "answerC": "C. Change",
      "answerD": "D. Return",
      "correct_answer": "C. Change"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Q9. What does the question mark (?) indicate? A particular is ...",
      "answerA": "A. Necessary",
      "answerB": "B. Missing",
      "answerC": "C. Optional",
      "answerD": "D. Changed",
      "correct_answer": "C. Optional"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Q10. What should you use to provide a default value for a variable in Swift?",
      "answerA": "A. ?",
      "answerB": "B. ??",
      "answerC": "C. &",
      "answerD": "D. &&",
      "correct_answer": "B. ??"
    },
  ]
}
